

DILA RIZVINA NATAISHA

| dilarnataisha@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/dilarizvinan | dila-rn.vercel.app

An Electrical Engineering graduate from Universitas Gadjah Mada who has a passion for Front- end Web Development. During her time in college, she engaged in various activities that allowed her to develop her communication, leadership, and problem-solving abilities. These experiences, combined with her knowledge, allow her to approach problems with both technical and creative solutions to bring a unique perspective and work collaboratively with others to achieve success.

Work Experiences

LUVIA Hijab Apr 2022 - Jun 2022

Graphic Designer

- As a graphic designer for LUVIA Hijab, I successfully created stunning designs for the LUVIA and LUVKID brands, including graphics for social media promotion, catalogues, and merchandise, using my expertise in Adobe Photoshop and Illustrator.
- In addition to my design work, I also particiated in product photography, photo editing, and video editing for LUVIA's social media
 content, ensuring that the brand's visual identity remained consistent and captivating to its audience.

PT Pertamina (Persero) RU VI Balongan

Jan 2021 - Feb 2021

Maintenance Execution Intern

• Throughout my month-long internship, I dedicated my research to studying catalyst level control in a regenerator for the Residue Catalytic Cracker Unit (RCC), gaining invaluable experience and insights about how the system works.

Departemen Teknik Elektro dan Teknologi Informasi FT UGM

Oct 2020 - Dec 2020

Laboratory Assistant of Digital and Microprocessor

- I was responsible for assisting the students to do lab works and simulations, such as Combinatorial Logic circuit, Digital Aritmethic,
 Digital I/O Microprocessor, and Analog I/O Microprocessor, all while honing my own skills with ESP32 Microcontrollers and Autodesk Tinkercad.
- Working with students on these critical concepts not only deepened my own understanding of these technologies, but also helped me
 to develop my abilities as an educator, enabling me to communicate complex ideas with clarity and confidence.

Education Level

Synrgy Academy Sep 2022 - Feb 2023

Certificate in Full-Stack Web Development

- SYNRGY Academy is a collaboration program between BCA and Binar Academy in the form of online bootcamp scholarship.
- During the six months of intensive online bootcamp, with project-based learning method, I learned about basic full-stack web
 development concepts such as responsive web design, object-oriented programming in JavaScript, DOM manipulation, building
 RESTful APIs and HTTP servers, creating single-page web applications, and projects deployment.
- I worked on the final project with 18 team members and was given the opportunity to lead as the Project Manager.
- Throughout the bootcamp, I enhanced my skills in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, React.js, Next.js, Node.js, Express.js, Sequelize, Railway, Vercel, CI/CD and Git.

Universitas Gadjah Mada - D.I. Yogyakarta

Aug 2018 - Oct 2022

Undergraduate in Electrical Engineering, 3.24/4.00

• During my studies in electrical engineering, I had the opportunity to gain a strong foundation in fundamental concepts and principles. Developed a comprehensive understanding of the various techniques and strategies used in control engineering, such as feedback control and proportional integral derivative (PID) control. Overall, my studies in electrical engineering equipped me with the knowledge and skills needed to excel in the field of control engineering.

Organisational Experience

KMTETI FT UGM Feb 2020 - Dec 2020

Vice Head of Information and Communication Division

- Assisted the Head of the Information and Communication Division in completing their duties, helping to complete a range of essential
 tasks, including designing the cabinet logo, editing and enhancing cabinet release photos, and fulfilling a wide range of graphic design
 needs for KMTETI FT UGM.
- As a member of Information and Communication Division, i took part in crafting visually stunning covers for announcements and special day celebrations to developing compelling designs for press releases, Voltamagz magazine, Voltanews Bulletin, and Infographics, I was committed to delivering high-quality work that caught the eye and captivated the attention of our audience while also delivering valuable content.

KMTETI FT UGM Jan 2019 - Feb 2020

Treasurer of Information and Communication Division

- · I was responsible for managing financial affairs, including financial planning, mapping and record-keeping, and financial reporting.
- Additionally, I played a key role in fulfilling the graphic design needs of KMTETI FT UGM, using my expertise in design to create visually stunning content that effectively conveyed important information to our audience.

JournARTIism 2019 Jun 2019 - Oct 2019

Head of Multimedia Team

- As the Head of the Multimedia Division for JournARTlism 2019, I managed the multimedia team to ensure all design needs were met for the event. This included creating eye-catching posters, banners, and covers for reminders.
- · Additionally, I actively participated in documenting the event to capture the spirit of the occasion.

PPSMB Kesatria FT UGM May 2019 - Aug 2019

Member of Design Division

- As a member of the Design Division, I was responsible for making ornaments and editing co-cards for staffs of PPSMB Kesatria 2019.
- · Created a design for an infographic called "Ngulik Teknik" to present pieces of information about the departments in FT UGM.

Find IT! UGM Oct 2018 - Apr 2019

Member of Multimedia Team

- Made icons to represent the competitions, poster for "Competitive Programming" competition, cover for announcements, cover for a proposal, and certificates.
- · Took a part in documenting the event.

Skills, Achievements & Other Experience

- Graphic Design: Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Corel Draw, Adobe Lightroom
- Frontend Web Development: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Next.js, React.js
- Backend Web Development: RESTful API, Express.js, PostgreSQL, Node.js, Railway
- Electrical Engineering Softwares: MatLAB, PSIM, LT Spice, Node- RED, InfluxDB, Grafana, PSIM.
- SBC and Microcontrollers: Raspberry Pi, Arduino, ESP32
- Other Programming language: Python, C++, C